team credit
Do you, Kazuomi, take Sayaka
as your lawfully wedded wife?
"The picture perfect husband and wife".
Not many guests, huh?
You think?
He's got looks, and a solid career.
He's wasted on her.
I can't stand them.
Lame.
She's practically begging for him.
Does she feel no shame?
- I do.
What a bore.
It's all practically routine at this point.
I've seen my fair share of weddings.
No one's ever objected at the altar,
nor suddenly professed their love
as a secret second suitor.
Won't something interesting happen for once?
- Congrats!
- Congratulations!
♫ ♫
Sakuraba.
Hello there.
I underestimated how nerve-racking
a wedding would be.
Your exhibition the other day was stunning.
Sayaka shared the same sentiments.
See this? We visited after receiving
our first-look photos.
I see.
Yes. We're excited to see your shots
from the ceremony as well.
Thank you.
I'll talk to you again later.
Looking good.
Let me get another shot.
Thank you.
This tastes great.
Blue champagne is a first, though.
It's a memorable drink to both Sayaka and I.
Hey, no getting wasted before the groom.
Are you alright?
Yes, sorry.
I haven't performed for a crowd in ages.
When did you begin learning violin?
When I was three years old.
Wow, that's quite young.
My mother insisted.
Then she must be excited
to hear you perform today.
I held my wedding at this venue as well.
You seem happy.
Don't worry, Mrs. Sayaka.
Happiness will find its way to you, too.
You've got something on your cheek.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Right there.
Well, look at that.
Jeez...
This has been a wonderful ceremony, ma'am.
Thank you. We appreciate you all
for coming to join us today.
Of course we'd come! We're Sayaka's besties.
Anything for her big day.
Yes, we're here for Sayaka.
Sayaka and I have both been blessed
with such wonderful friends.
You're embarrassing us.
Guests, thank you for your patience.
Mrs. Sayaka will now be performing
the violin for you all.
Please enjoy her performance.
Go, Sayaka!
You got this!
Give it your all.
Sayaka!
- Is she drunk?
- That can't be it.
- Sayaka!
- Why?
- Someone call an ambulance!
- Wake up, please!
- Sayaka! Sayaka!
What in the world is going on?
- Am I dreaming?
- We need an ambulance. It's an emergency.
I'm treading into the unknown.
This hell unfolding before me
- is far from the routine I'm used to.
- Sayaka...
Sayaka.
Sayaka!
Come here.
The bride collapsed while spitting up blood.
What if someone had an ulterior motive
at that wedding?
How could this have happened?
And during the wedding, no less...
How absolutely embarrassing.
What?
Goodness...
[Unhappiest wishes to you, Red Riding Hood]
Mother.
Sayaka never had any health issues, correct?
Then we ought to report this after all.
Absolutely not.
Not the police.
But Mother...
Think this through, dear.
The wedding was already chaotic,
and now you wish to get the police involved?
These sorts of rumors spread quick.
But for Sayaka to remain at ease...
Listen to me, Kazuomi.
I truly appreciate you
getting defensive on my daughter's behalf.
But please, calm yourself for a moment.
Sayaka won't feel any better
knowing you blew this out of proportion.
Isn't that right?
Sakuraba?
I apologize for visiting unannounced.
Wait, how did you get my address?
"How"?
Think back to when you visited my exhibition.
Thank you.
[Name - Address - Phone number]
Right, I forgot.
Who is that at the door?
Oh, this is...
The name's Sakuraba, ma'am.
I was the wedding photographer.
I apologize for the trouble
our ceremony caused.
Actually, I have some shots from yesterday.
Would you like to take a look?
My, these all look wonderful.
This was to be their moment, and yet...
I think I'll get going.
Kazuomi. Keep in mind what I told you.
Right, of course. I won't say a thing.
Remember, this is for Sayaka.
Here you go.
Thank you.
What brings you here today, Sakuraba?
There's something I believe
you ought to know.
I apologize if I'm meddling, but please.
Take a look for yourself.
I find issue with the second photograph.
Is there something wrong here?
Look carefully.
Your wife's champagne.
Does it not look odd to you?
It's a darker blue.
Isn't this a matter of lighting?
Impossible.
Her drink would not be this shade of blue,
even if her glass were covered by a shadow.
She was poisoned?
I do not know.
But I couldn't bear to keep this to myself.
Sakuraba!
Sakuraba! Sakuraba!
I finally caught up.
It's like I was screaming to a wall.
Could I get that photograph you showed me?
I can't let this slide.
Sayaka was poisoned.
That's why...
I plan to find the culprit myself.
Yourself? Why not report this to the police?
I have my circumstances.
Though I'm only a civil servant,
I'll do what I can to uncover the truth.
I can still file a report
after I've exhausted my own options.
I understand.
I'll send the pictures to you when I return.
Though there are quite a few...
Sakuraba.
I vow to find this culprit.
Still, I feel rather uncertain
working alone.
If possible...
Could you please assist me?
Assist you...
In finding the culprit?
Yes.
I think you should file a report after all.
Besides, I'm only a photographer.
But, Sakuraba...
Sorry.
[Town Hall]
Sir, you forgot to specify
if this is your first marriage or not.
You're right. I completely missed that.
In that case, if you could please...
Here's a file for you.
Thanks.
We sure are busy today.
Must be a lucky day.
Did you submit your papers on a lucky day?
Sure did.
You filed your marriage at your own office.
How did that feel?
Get back to work.
Hey, no need to be so prickly.
Or what, did something happen at the wedding?
Kazuomi.
Want to grab lunch?
Sure.
Quit cracking jokes, and start filing papers.
Yes, sir.
Thanks.
What for?
Kazu.
Welcome home.
Not the police.
I think you should file a report after all.
Besides, I'm only a photographer.
Sakuraba, are you home?
This is Hayashida.
Sakuraba.
Sakuraba!
- Sakuraba.
- Huh?
Sachiko?
Sakuraba.
Please, lend me your strength.
I need your help in finding the culprit.
Why me?
You know better than anyone
what occurred at that venue.
But more importantly,
you're the only other person who knows
that Sayaka may have been poisoned.
Still...
Sayaka and I...
We were to become husband and wife.
I promised I would be by her side.
I vowed to protect her.
And yet...
I can still see Sayaka collapsing.
It's been seared to the back of my eyelids.
So that's why...
That's why...
I can't let things end like this.
I won't forgive whoever harmed my wife.
You noticed the darker champagne.
You noticed something I never would have.
I can trust you, Sakuraba.
My gut's telling me I can.
Please.
Please help me, for Sayaka's sake.
Please, I beg you.
Please.
Please, help me.
Fine.
What?
I'm the one who informed you
of the potential poisoning.
I feel a bit responsible
for seeing this through.
Really?
You'll help me?
Sure.
Thank you!
I knew you were a good man.
Personal space.
Just one thing.
Don't expect much from me, okay?
It's not like I'm a detective or anything.
I'm as much of an amateur as you are.
But there is one thing I can say for sure.
All attendees of the wedding are suspects.
And that includes the man
whose eyes I met first.
That's right.
He's just as much of a suspect, too.
Truth be told, I actually have one lead.
A lead?
The day before our ceremony...
this letter was left in our mailbox.